{
  "id": "MA3095",
  "introvideo": "hint1.mp4",
  "IntroText": {
    "Type": "PlainText",
    "Content": "想一想，再選選看"
  },
  "GameType": "SelfDefine",
  "GameConfig": {
    "GlobalTitle": "[Insert title.]"
  },
  "Hint": {},
  "Questions": [
    [
      {
        "Question": "下面哪些蛋糕有顏色的部分是\\frac{4}{8}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 4,
        "Denominator": 8,
        "Factors": [4, 2],
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 3,
        "Color": "lightgreen",
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些蛋糕有顏色的部分是\\frac{3}{8}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 3,
        "Denominator": 8,
        "Factors": [4, 2],
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 2,
        "Color": "lightgreen",
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些蛋糕有顏色的部分是\\frac{2}{8}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 2,
        "Denominator": 8,
        "Factors": [4, 2],
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 3,
        "Color": "lightgreen",
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些蛋糕有顏色的部分是\\frac{5}{8}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 5,
        "Denominator": 8,
        "Factors": [4, 2],
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 4,
        "Color": "lightgreen",
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些蛋糕有顏色的部分是\\frac{6}{8}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 6,
        "Denominator": 8,
        "Factors": [4, 2],
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 1,
        "Color": "green",
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕"
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Question": "哪些緞帶有顏色的部分是\\frac{8}{11}？",
        "Type": "Ribbon",
        "Numerator": 8,
        "Denominator": 11,
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 2,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕",
        "Color": "orange"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些緞帶有顏色的部分是\\frac{5}{11}？",
        "Type": "Ribbon",
        "Numerator": 5,
        "Denominator": 11,
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 3,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕",
        "Color": "orange"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些緞帶有顏色的部分是\\frac{7}{11}？",
        "Type": "Ribbon",
        "Numerator": 7,
        "Denominator": 11,
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 1,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕",
        "Color": "orange"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些緞帶有顏色的部分是\\frac{2}{11}？",
        "Type": "Ribbon",
        "Numerator": 2,
        "Denominator": 11,
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 2,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕",
        "Color": "orange"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些緞帶有顏色的部分是\\frac{6}{11}？",
        "Type": "Ribbon",
        "Numerator": 6,
        "Denominator": 11,
        "Option": 5,
        "CorrectOption": 4,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個蛋糕",
        "Color": "orange"
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Question": "哪些巧克力有顏色的部分\\frac{1}{6}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 1,
        "Denominator": 6,
        "Factors": [2, 3],
        "Option": 6,
        "CorrectOption": 2,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個巧克力",
        "Color": "brown"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些巧克力有顏色的部分\\frac{2}{6}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 2,
        "Denominator": 6,
        "Factors": [2, 3],
        "Option": 6,
        "CorrectOption": 1,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個巧克力",
        "Color": "brown"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些巧克力有顏色的部分\\frac{3}{6}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 3,
        "Denominator": 6,
        "Factors": [2, 3],
        "Option": 6,
        "CorrectOption": 3,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個巧克力",
        "Color": "brown"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些巧克力有顏色的部分\\frac{4}{6}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 4,
        "Denominator": 6,
        "Factors": [2, 3],
        "Option": 6,
        "CorrectOption": 2,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個巧克力",
        "Color": "brown"
      },
      {
        "Question": "哪些巧克力有顏色的部分\\frac{5}{6}？",
        "Type": "Paper",
        "Numerator": 5,
        "Denominator": 6,
        "Factors": [2, 3],
        "Option": 6,
        "CorrectOption": 2,
        "Itemdescription": "這是一個巧克力",
        "Color": "brown"
      }
    ]
  ]
}
